# Shashank SK

## I will immediately join for graphic designing job.

Jalahalli, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560090 shashankkambanour4\_nb7@indeedemail.com +918971335895

I am a Graphic Designer with creative and technical expertise. I have over 6 years of experience in Industry, designs for social media, UI design, fabric design printing & print media. Additional basic skills in Operating Printers, Microsoft PowerPoints, Microsoft Word. Personally I believe that quality and perfection require focus and continued efforts.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

#### Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1992-08-08 Eligible to work in: India

**Highest Career Level:** 5+ years experience

**Industry:** Advertising, PR, MR, Event Management, Arts & Entertainment, Healthcare, Human Resources, Internet, Ecommerce, Marketing, Media & Communications, NGO, Social Services, Regulators, Industry Associations, Pharmacy, Publishing, Real Estate, Sales, Technology

Total years of experience: 6

## Work Experience

#### **Graphic Designer**

The Akshaya Patra Foundation - Bengaluru, Karnataka December 2022 to January 2024

Offical Blog, SEO Article, Quora, Infographic, Mailer, HTML Coding, Website Banner, Landing Page Banner, FB Ads, GDN Ads, Youtube, Google Business, WhatsApp, Feedify, Donation Strip, Guest, HopeStory, Pinterest, Inshort, Way2New, BrandinMotion, Razorpay, News, Press Coverage, Press Release, Image Croping.

#### **Graphic Designer**

New Horizon College of Engineering - Bengaluru, Karnataka July 2022 to December 2022

Invitation, WhatsApp, Visitors ID, Banner, Poster, Certificate, Social Media, Presentation Standee, PhotoBooth Front & Back, Blog, Webinar, Instagram, Syllabus Cover Page, Exhibition Banner, Calendar of Events Semester, Graduation Day Book, Rank Banner, PG Graduation Day Book.

### **Graphic Designer**

Synergia Foundation - Bengaluru, Karnataka March 2021 to January 2022 Magazine Cover Page, Magazine Back Page, Magazine Index Page, Magazine Inside Page, Magazine Layout, Infographic, Promo Video, Trailer Video, Full Video, Seminar Post, Calendar, Flyer, PPT, Newsletter, Social Media, ID Card, Coffee Table, Christmas & New Year, Image Editing

#### **Graphic Designer**

Right Gifting Solutions - Bengaluru, Karnataka February 2020 to May 2020

Printing Advertisement Design, Pattern Design, Brand Logo designs on to Fabric Material Example Drop Down banner, Dangler, Hand Flag, Face Mask, Curve Flag, Tear Flag, L Banner, Oblix Standee. Catalogue Book, Pamphlet, Visiting Card, T-Shirt Sport, Infographic, Logo Design, Icon, Flyer, Brochure.

#### **Graphic Designer**

Capricot Technologies Pvt Ltd - Bengaluru, Karnataka April 2019 to May 2019

Social Media, Post, Blog, Print, Marketing

## **Graphic Designer**

WinWire Technologies - Bengaluru, Karnataka June 2018 to November 2018

Blog Web Banner, Brochure, Ebook Design, Email Design, Event Images Collages, Infographic Poster Design, Newsletter, Website Mockup, Notebook, Office Work Design, Signature Banner, Social Media, Standee, Testimonial, Webinar, EDM Design, Event Post Design, Event Poster Design, Office Entrance Board Design.

## **Graphic Designer**

Out Thinking Pvt Ltd - Bengaluru, Karnataka May 2016 to May 2018

Print Media, Social Media, Ui Design, Screenshot, App Icon, Picture Graphic - Android App Of Google Play Store, Phone Cases Design, Couple Phone Case Design, Infographic, Standee Design, Thank You For Shopping Design, Mail Post Design, Web Banner, T-Shirt Design, Wall Poster Design, Mug Design, Greeting Cards, Product Image Enhancement, Product Video, Svg, Brochures, Logo Design.

### **Graphic Designer**

Fiverr - Bengaluru, Karnataka September 2015 to April 2016

Highly Creative & Multi Tasking Graphic Designer In Graphics For Digital Marketing, Mobile Graphics, Illustrator Designs, Photo Editing, Free Hand Design, Print Publication Design, Logo, Brochure, Poster, Info Graphic, Banner And More.

### **Graphic Designer**

BMS INNOLABS PVT LTD - Bengaluru, Karnataka February 2014 to October 2014

Designing Alphabet character design and car, house, panda, Jewellery, Corn character

#### Education

## **Diploma in Graphic Design**

Arena Animation - Bengaluru, Karnataka 2013

### **Diploma in Electrical (CoE)**

Govt Industrial Training Institute - Bengaluru, Karnataka August 2008 to August 2010

## Secondary(10th Pass) in SSLC

M.E.C English High School - Bengaluru, Karnataka 2008

## Skills / IT Skills

- Adobe Photoshop (6 years)
- Adobe Illustrator (6 years)
- Corel Draw (4 years)
- Adobe Indesign (6 years)
- Adobe Premier Pro (6 years)
- Microsoft Word (6 years)
- Microsoft PowerPoint (3 years)
- Graphic design (6 years)
- Adobe Creative Suite (6 years)
- Communication skills (6 years)
- Adobe Dreamweaver (1 year)

### Languages

- English Fluent
- Kannada Fluent
- Hindi Fluent

#### Online Profile

https://www.behance.net/shashankskindia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/shashank-sk-53274512a/

#### Certifications and Licenses

#### **Design Suite**

2012 to Present

Certification body: Performance Statement

# 2D Design & Animation Suite

2013 to Present

Certification body: Performance Statement

# Additional Information

Music Keyboard & Traveling